adultmovies.com 2019-02-11

# Privacy Policy | AdultMovies

The operator of this web site is WMM Holdings, LLC ("Service Provider"). The Service Provider recognizes customers, visitors, users, and others who use the web site and values their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the web site. Service Provider provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the web site. Last Updated: July 9, 2015. Last Reviewed: July 9, 2015. 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Service Provider's Terms of Use. Your use of the web site and any personal information you provide on the web site remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use, and any other documentation we may publish or provide from time to time. 

## The Information Service Provider Collects

  * **Cookies Information:** When you visit the web site, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters \- to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Service Provider uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the web site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 
  * **Log File Information:** When you use the web site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit page URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * **Clear Gifs Information:** When you use the web site, we may employ "clear gifs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our Users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 

## The Way Service Provider Retains Information

  * To preserve the integrity of web site databases, Service Provider's procedure is to retain information for an indefinite length of time. Any information submitted to or collected by Service Provider shall be stored indefinitely and by use of the web site you consent to such storage. 
  * If required by law, Service Provider will scramble and/or encrypt that information to make it unrecognizable. Service Provider will also respond to written member requests to scramble account information. If you wish to make such a request, which will require you to verify your identity, contact the [Service Provider Policy Manager](mailto:billing@theadultmovieservice.com "Service Provider Policy Manager"). 

## The Way Service Provider Uses Information

  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major web site changes or for customer service purposes). 
  * We may use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the web site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the web site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

## When Service Provider Discloses Information

  * We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf (for example: credit card processing). We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 
  * We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit page URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the web site and to provide services. 
  * We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, law enforcement request, or search warrant. 
  * Service Provider also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Service Provider believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Service Provider, our Users or others. 

## Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the web site, in which case Service Provider may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the web site, if any, cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

Please contact Service Provider with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices by emailing [customer service](mailto:support@theadultmovieservice.com "customer service"). 

## Our Commitment To Data Security:

Service Provider uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Service Provider and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Service Provider makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Service Provider learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Service Provider may post a notice on the web site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify [customer service](mailto:support@theadultmovieservice.com "customer service"). 

## Our Commitment to Legal-Age Usage

Protecting children from adult content is especially important. For that reason, Service Provider does not allow users under the age of 18, or knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the web site from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18, or legal age according to state law. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the web site at any time or in any manner. If Service Provider learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected on the web site then Service Provider will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

## Special Note to International Users:

The web site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States following and complying with the laws of the United States. We understand the nature of web sites being accessible throughout the world and we do not block or refuse transactions from non-US countries or citizens. If you are a User accessing the web site from any region in the world with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the web site, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, our Terms of Use, and any other documents we may publish or provide to you from time to time which govern the use of the web site, you are transferring your personal information to the United States, subject only to the laws of the United States, and you consent to that transfer and waive any objection thereto under the laws of your jurisdiction, international laws, treaties, or any other rule, regulation, or guideline. 

## In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that Service Provider is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

## Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and users are encouraged to review the Notices periodically to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the web site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. 

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.
